The Man Nobody Knew: In Search of My Father, CIA Spymaster William Colby is
a drama, documentary, history film directed by Carl Colby.
A personal exploration into the life of America's controversial former CIA
Director told through the eyes of his wife and filmmaker son, Carl.
Through extraordinary events in twentieth century history, this consummate soldier/spy stood
at the center of the Agency's most clandestine activities and operations.
The film reveals the 'cover life' of this CIA operative, who followed orders and took on the dirtiest assignments until
the Nixon Administration ordered him to 'stonewall' Congress about the CIA's past abuses, but he refused.
This film reveals why, for the first time, he could not obey.
Self (archive footage), played by William Colby.
Self - Former National Security Advisor, played by Zbigniew Brzezinski.
Self, played by Seymour Hersh.
Self, played by Donald Rumsfeld.
Self (archive footage), played by George H. W. Bush.
Self (archive footage), played by John F. Kennedy.
The Man Nobody Knew: In Search of My Father, CIA Spymaster William Colby is a 2011 American
documentary film exploring the life and career of former CIA director William Colby.
The tone is emotional.